A Guide to the Markle Foundation records, Accessions 1997-2008, Record Group 4 FA785
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Edith Bjornson Files, 1982-1998; 7; 30.23 Cubic Feet 23 standard record storage boxes
  - Roger Schank - Northwestern, 1997-1998 (Box 115, Folder 41)
  - Siegel and Gale (Box 115, Folder 42-43)
  - Miscellaneous - S (Box 115, Folder 44)
  - Erik Sandberg-Diment (Box 115, Folder 45-46)
  - Roger Schank - Northwestern, 1996-1997 (Box 115, Folder 47-51)
  - Scholastic Inc., 1994 (Box 115, Folder 52)
  - Michael Schrage, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 53-54)
  - Evan Schwartz - Tufts University, 1994-1996 (Box 115, Folder 55-57)
  - Shanley, Lorraine (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Siegel and Gale (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - David Sit, 1992-1996 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Hendrick L. Smith (Box 116, Folder 4-5)
  - Social Venture Capital (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Speech File (Box 116, Folder 7-8)
  - Miscellaneous - T-U (Box 116, Folder 9-13)
  - Thornburn, David, MIT (Box 116, Folder 14-21)
  - Miscellaneous - V (Box 116, Folder 22-26)
  - Venture Capital (Box 116, Folder 27-29)
  - Tracy Westen - Elizabeth Virgo (Box 116, Folder 30)
  - Reinventing America (REUS) II - Wunderman Cato Johnson (Box 116, Folder 31-40)
  - Dyson - Governor Pataki's Task Force - Wiring Schools, 1993; 1998 (Box 116, Folder 41-42)
  - NY Wired Meeting, 1998 February 12 (Box 116, Folder 43)
  - Miscelleneous - E (Box 116, Folder 44)
  - Electronic Town Meetings - Meeting and Debrief (Box 116, Folder 45-50)
  - Email Study (Box 116, Folder 51-57)
  - Email - Universal (Box 117, Folder 1-4)
  - Miscellaneous - F (Box 117, Folder 5-11)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC) (Box 117, Folder 12-15)
  - Joel Fleishman (Box 117, Folder 16-21)
  - Foundations, 1992 (Box 117, Folder 22-25)
  - Miscellaneous - G, 1996-1997 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Game Producers (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Gartner Group - IAC (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - Henry Geller - Participation in Reinventing America (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - Henry Geller - Cable Controversy, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - Peter Goldmark - PBS Material, 1997 (Box 117, Folder 31)
  - Gordon, Alexandra, 1995 (Box 117, Folder 32)
  - Grossman, Larry (Box 117, Folder 33-36)
  - Miscellaneous - H (Box 117, Folder 37-43)
  - Health Care (Box 117, Folder 44-49)
  - IAG, 1997-1998 (Box 117, Folder 50-51)
  - Miscellaneous - K (Box 117, Folder 52)
  - Henry A. Kaplan - HAK Associates (Box 117, Folder 53)
  - Dan Klores Associates, MIT (Box 117, Folder 54)
  - Markle Foundation Financial - Budget Tracking on Projects, 1993-1997 (Box 117, Folder 55-58)
  - Markle Foundation Grants and Program Charts, Mission, Objectives, 1993-1997 (Box 117, Folder 59-63)
  - Markle Grants List, 1996-1998 (Box 117, Folder 64)
  - Markle Grants 1970-1993 and Program Charts, 1995-1997 (Box 117, Folder 65)
  - Life Plan Center (Gladys Thatcher), 1997 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous - I (Box 118, Folder 2-5)
  - Infonautics Corporation, 1995-1998 (Box 118, Folder 6-8)
  - Interactive Miscellaneous (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - International Advisory Council (IAC) (Box 118, Folder 10-28)
  - Miscellaneous - J-K (Box 118, Folder 29-36)
  - Miscellaneous - L, 1996-1998 (Box 118, Folder 37-39)
  - Lasker Foundation (Box 118, Folder 40)
  - Lloyd N. Morrisett - Lecture Series, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 41-43)
  - Lloyd N. Morrisett - Tribute (Box 118, Folder 44-49)
  - Miscellaneous - M, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 50-51)
  - Markle Foundation, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 52-56)
  - Markle Foundation - Book and 70th Year Celebration, 1996-1998 (Box 118, Folder 57-60)
  - Markle Foundation - Executive Search and Transition Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 118, Folder 61-64)
  - Markle Foundation - Website, 1996-1997 (Box 118, Folder 65)
  - Mickiewicz, Ellen, 1996-1997 (Box 118, Folder 66-67)
  - Matrix Game - International Advsiory Council (IAC), 1997 (Box 118, Folder 68)
  - Lee Mitgang, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 69)
  - Bruce Murray, 1993-1996 (Box 118, Folder 70-72)
  - Miscellaneous - N (Box 118, Folder 73-77)
  - Miscellaneous - National (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - National Press Foundation, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - New York New Media Association, 1994-1998 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - New York University (Box 119, Folder 4-6)
  - Night Kitchen - Bob Stein, 1997-1998 (Box 119, Folder 7-15)
  - Miscellaneous - O (Box 119, Folder 16-20)
  - O'Neill, Richard (Box 119, Folder 21-26)
  - Ornstein, Norman (Box 119, Folder 27-28)
  - Miscellaneous - P (Box 119, Folder 29-38)
  - DVD, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 39)
  - Program Exploration, 1997-1998 (Box 119, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous - Q-R (Box 119, Folder 41)
  - Monroe Price, 1994-1998 (Box 119, Folder 42-51)
  - Monroe Price (Box 120, Folder 1-2)
  - Princeton Survey Research Association, 1997 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Pro-Natura (Box 120, Folder 4-6)
  - Jonathan Zemmol, 1997 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Program Exploration - Children's Programming, 1998 (Box 120, Folder 8-9)
  - Medical Project, 1998 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Program Exploration - Journalism, 1997-1998 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Proposal Evaluations (Box 120, Folder 12-13)
  - Program Retreats, 1998 (Box 120, Folder 14-15)
  - ADASPO - Role of the Board in a Small Company, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Broadcasting, Society and Policy in Multimedia Age (Graham-Davies), 1988 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - DYG - American Political Channel (APC) Project, 1994-1996 (Box 120, Folder 18-19)
  - Annual Report of the USA, 1994-1995 (Box 120, Folder 20-21)
  - Aspen Institute - Conference - Wye Woods - Twenty-First Century TV, 1992 February 3-4 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Aspen Institute - Communications and Society Program, 1992-1995 (Box 120, Folder 23-26)
  - Benjamin Bather, Rutgers University, 1995 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - David Bollier - Draft of Paper on Home Video for Niche Programming, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - David Bollier - The Rise and Fall of the Media Reform Movement, 1988-1994 (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - Bruce Buchanan, 1988-1992 (Box 120, Folder 30-33)
  - Red Burns - Alternative Media Center, 1978-1987 (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - David Brin - Cal Tech - "The Good and the Bad: Outlines of Tomorrow" Transcript, 1993 October (Box 120, Folder 35)
  - Broadband Networks, John Carey, Greyston, 1988-1995 (Box 120, Folder 36)
  - Carter Commission, 1993 (Box 121, Folder 1-2)
  - The Annie E. Casey Foundation, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Columbia Journalism Review Material, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Conferences - Columbia, 1998 (Box 121, Folder 5-6)
  - Conferences - Miscellaneous - A, 1996-1997 (Box 121, Folder 7-9)
  - Commerce and Community, 1997 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Copyright and New Media, 1997 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Sara Czaja, 1994 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Communitarianism - Amitai Etzioni, 1997 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Concord Coalition, 1993 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Copyright and Intellectual Property, 1988-1992 (Box 121, Folder 15-16)
  - Copyright and Intellectual Property - Wye Woods papers, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - Crossover Technologies - Technology Solutions, Inc. (TSI) (Presidential Election and Reinventing America Projects), 1996 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - Crossover Technologies - Presidential Election and Reinventing America Projects, 1995-1996 (Box 121, Folder 19-21)
  - Charles A. Dana Foundation - Suzanne Sunshine, 1996 (Box 121, Folder 22)
  - Crossover Technologies - Reinventing America (REUS) Project, 1994-1995 (Box 121, Folder 23)
  - Duke University - Ethiopia Conference, 1998 February (Box 121, Folder 24)
  - DYG - American Political Channel (APC) Project (Box 121, Folder 25-27)
  - Electronic Media and the First Amendment, Wye Woods Conference, 1990 June (Box 121, Folder 28)
  - Electronic Town Meetings, 1992-1994 (Box 121, Folder 29-33)
  - Electronic Town Meetings - Al Perlmutter and Larry Greene, 1994-1995 (Box 121, Folder 34-35)
  - Electronic Town Meetings - Al Perlmutter and Larry Greene, 1991-1995 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Henry Geller, 1987-1995 (Box 122, Folder 2-11)
  - Larry Grossman, 1992-1996 (Box 122, Folder 12-13)
  - Harper Collins, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 14-16)
  - Harvard University, 1990-1996 (Box 122, Folder 15-20)
  - Health, 1994-1998 (Box 122, Folder 21-23)
  - HomeNet Affiliates Meeting, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 24)
  - Internet, 1994-1998 (Box 122, Folder 25-30)
  - Journalism (Box 122, Folder 31)
  - KIDSNET (Karen Jaffe), 1997-1998 (Box 122, Folder 32)
  - Learning, 1991-1997 (Box 122, Folder 33-35)
  - Peter Lyman, Berkeley, 1995-1996 (Box 122, Folder 36)
  - Manhattan Institute - Regulation of Broadcast Industry, 1990 March 28 (Box 122, Folder 37)
  - Carter Center - E. Mickiewicz - Russian Survey Grant and Follow-Up, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 38-39)
  - MIT Conference - Interactivity and Political Participation, 1991 July (Box 122, Folder 40-42)
  - Bruce Murray - Challenges of the Twenty-First Century, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Tom Patterson - Progress Report, 1991 June (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Political Advertising and the First Amendment, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Prodigy - Tim Zagat, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - PBS - Boston Consulting Study, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 5-6)
  - PBS - The Voters Channel-Voters Voice (TVC, TVV), 1990-1991 (Box 123, Folder 7-9)
  - Public Interest and Public Relations, 1989-1993 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Public Agenda - Board, 1996 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Public Agenda - Online-Current Opinion Research Project, 1996 (Box 123, Folder 12-14)
  - Public Agenda Foundation, 1995-1997 (Box 123, Folder 15-16)
  - Public Agenda - Journalists Project, 1994-1997 (Box 123, Folder 17-18)
  - PBS - Technology Summits for Educators, 1993; 1996 (Box 123, Folder 19-20)
  - PBS - Restructure - 20th Century Study, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - Public Relations Firms - Potentials, 1995-1997 (Box 123, Folder 22-23)
  - Miscellaneous - Q-R (Box 123, Folder 24-28)
  - RAND, 1993-1996 (Box 123, Folder 29-33)
  - Recontact Study - Kansas, Mass., 1996-1998 (Box 123, Folder 34)
  - Recontact Study - DKA, Inc. - Kansas, Mass., 1996 (Box 123, Folder 35)
  - Norval Reece, 1991-1995 (Box 123, Folder 36-37)
  - RGA Interactive (Box 123, Folder 38-40)
  - Reinventing America (REUS) I - Crossover and Owen Comora, 1995-1997 (Box 124, Folder 1-12)
  - Reinventing America (REUS) I - STARS - Frank Leicht, 1995-1996 (Box 124, Folder 13-15)
  - Reinventing America (REUS) II - STARS - Frank Leicht, 1996-1997 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Reinventing America (REUS) II, 1996 (Box 124, Folder 17-24)
  - SimHealth - Press Conference and Briefings, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 25)
  - Markle Foundation - 1988-1991 - Media-Election Grants (Box 124, Folder 26-27)
- Accession 2000:016: Grants and General Files, 1968-1998; 8; 42.05 Cubic Feet 32 standard record storage boxes.
  Contains grant administration files, general files, and grant-related files, correspondence and reports.
  - Grantee Guidelines, Grant Review and Oversight (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - A - General, 1989-1996 (Box 158, Folder 2-5)
  - ABC Television, 1980-1995 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Abrams and Company Publishers, 1991 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Academic Systems Corporation, 1993-1994 (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Academy of Television Arts and Sciences Foundation, 1993 (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - Gene Accas, 1978-1994 (Box 158, Folder 10-11)
  - Accel Partners, 1993 (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Richard Adler, 1996-1997 (Box 158, Folder 13)
  - Access '87 (EBJ), 1987 (Box 158, Folder 14)
  - American Film Institute (AFI) (EBJ), 1989 (Box 158, Folder 15)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League (EBJ), 1990-1992 (Box 158, Folder 16)
  - American Newspaper Publishers Association (EBJ), 1988 (Box 158, Folder 17)
  - Christopher Arterton, 1991 (Box 158, Folder 18)
  - Paul Attewell (CUNY) (EBJ), 1991 (Box 158, Folder 19)
  - Aging (EBJ), 1986-1989 (Box 158, Folder 20-26)
  - The Allies, Inc., 1993 (Box 158, Folder 27)
  - Franz Allina, 1981; 1987-1992 (Box 158, Folder 28-29)
  - Action for Children's Television (Peggy Charren), 1979-1992 (Box 158, Folder 30-34)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Daniel Bell (G89325), 1989-1998 (Box 158, Folder 35-40)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - General, 1994 (Box 158, Folder 41)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (D94101), 1993-1994 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - American Center for Children's Television, 1993 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - American Center for Children's Television (D96102) (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - American Enterprise Institute, 1989-1996 (Box 171, Folder 8-9)
  - American Enterprise Institute (D95215), 1995-1996 (Box 171, Folder 10)
  - American Enterprise Institute (G92336), 1992-1995 (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - Brookings Institution (G92337) (Box 171, Folder 12-13)
  - American Film Institute (AFI) (G93111), 1992-1996 (Box 171, Folder 14-18)
  - American Public Radio (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Foundation Center - Engelhardt (D94214), 1993 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - The William and Flora Hewlett Foundation, 1990 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Jocelyn Hidi, 1993 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - High Definition Television (HDTV) (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - High Scope Educational Research Foundation and ReSource Newsletter, 1990 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Hilde T. Himmelweit (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Hill and Knowlton, 1989-1990 (Box 168, Folder 6-7)
  - Hispanics in Philanthropy, 1989-1994 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - Roland Homet, 1981-1996 (Box 168, Folder 9-13)
  - Roland Homet - 2017:FA785:008 - International Crossroads Pilot Program, VHS, 17:45 minutes. (Box 2017:FA785:008)
  - Hoover Institute, 1982-1990 (Box 168, Folder 14)
  - Hoso Bunka Foundation, Japan, 1985-1989 (Box 168, Folder 15)
  - Hundt, Reed, 1996 (Box 168, Folder 16)
  - Sierra Online (INN), 1993 (Box 168, Folder 17-18)
  - I - General, 1978-1996 (Box 159, Folder 2-7)
  - University of Illinois, 1975-1990 (Box 159, Folder 8-10)
  - Illinois State University, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - AT&T and INN (Imagination Network), 1994 (Box 159, Folder 13-17)
  - Independent Production Fund - Perlmutter (G90009), 1990 (Box 159, Folder 18)
  - Independent Production Fund - Perlmutter (G94333), 1994 (Box 159, Folder 19)
  - Independent Sector (IS) (D92220) (Box 159, Folder 20)
  - Independent Sector (IS) (91218), 1991 (Box 159, Folder 21)
  - Independent Sector (IS) (D90318), 1989-1990 (Box 159, Folder 22)
  - Independent Sector (IS) (D90210), 1990-1991 (Box 159, Folder 23)
  - Independent Sector (IS) (D98222), 1998 (Box 159, Folder 24)
  - Independent Sector (IS) (D96318, D97220), 1996-1998 (Box 159, Folder 25)
  - Independent Sector (IS) (D95213, D94121, D93221), 1993-1996 (Box 159, Folder 26)
  - Infonautics - Board of Directors, 1993-1997 (Box 160, Folder 1-13)
  - Infonautics - Board of Directors, 1995-1997 (Box 161, Folder 1-7)
  - Infonautics (G94017) (Box 163, Folder 9-14)
  - Infonautics (G94017) (Box 164, Folder 1-6)
  - Innovative Communications Europe - Sue Lloyd, 1989-1990 (Box 161, Folder 8-9)
  - Independent Sector (IS), 1981-1993 (Box 161, Folder 10-16)
  - Independent Sector (IS), 1994-1997 (Box 162, Folder 1-6)
  - Institute of Design, 1996 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Institute for the Future, 1978-1991 (Box 162, Folder 8-14)
  - Institute of Gerontology, 1987-1989 (Box 162, Folder 15-16)
  - Institute for Information Studies - Wye Plantation, 1989 (Box 162, Folder 17)
  - Institute for Research on Learning, 1989-1993 (Box 162, Folder 18-20)
  - InterACTics, Inc., 1993 (Box 162, Folder 21)
  - Interactivity Media and Interactivity Video (Box 162, Folder 22-27)
  - International Broadcast Institute, 1970-1973 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - International Institute of Communications, 1984-1992 (Box 163, Folder 2-4)
  - International Management Group (IMG), 1993 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - International Telecommunications Possible Program Topic, 1991 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - IRIS, 1987-1992 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Israel Institute of Applied Social Research (D92329), 1992-1994 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - J - General, 1990-1997 (Box 164, Folder 7-11)
  - Thomas Jefferson Center for the Protection of Free Expression, 1990-1997 (Box 164, Folder 12-13)
  - Jefferson Center - O'Neil (D93330, 1993 (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Jerry Apodaco, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 15)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1974-1980 (Box 164, Folder 16)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1973-1992 (Box 164, Folder 17-20)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1975-1994 (Box 164, Folder 21-23)
  - Junk Proposals, 1993-1996 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - K - General, 1989-1996 (Box 165, Folder 2-6)
  - Kaiser Foundation, 1974-1994 (Box 165, Folder 7-8)
  - Kansas State, 1977-1995 (Box 165, Folder 9-11)
  - The Louis Guttman Israel Institute of Applied Social Research, 1991-1992 (Box 165, Folder 12)
  - Kent State - Bartolini, William, 1997 (Box 165, Folder 13)
  - KERA Dallas, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 14)
  - Kettering Foundation, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 15)
  - Kids Count, 1990 (Box 165, Folder 16)
  - KidsNet, 1990-1992 (Box 165, Folder 17)
  - Kids Voting, 1990 (Box 165, Folder 18)
  - Thomas J. Klutzick Co., 1991-1994 (Box 165, Folder 19)
  - The Knight Foundation, 1990-1995 (Box 165, Folder 20)
  - Peter Kohler, 1992 (Box 165, Folder 21)
  - KQED, 1989-1995 (Box 165, Folder 22-23)
  - Kopp, Katherine, 1996 (Box 165, Folder 24)
  - KTCA Minneapolis, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 25)
  - L - General, 1989-1997 (Box 165, Folder 26-32)
  - Lambert and Weiss, 1995-1996 (Box 165, Folder 33)
  - League of Women Voters, 1980-1996 (Box 165, Folder 34-37)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund (D92219), 1992-1993 (Box 165, Folder 38)
  - The Learning Channel, 1983-1985; 1991-1992 (Box 165, Folder 39-40)
  - University of Leeds, 1976-1990 (Box 166, Folder 1-3)
  - Frank Leicht, Consultant, 1989-1995 (Box 166, Folder 4-5)
  - Leonardo - General, 1996 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - Lilly Endowment, 1976-1990 (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - Lochridge and Company, Inc., 1994 (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - London Business School, 1989-1995 (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - London Business School (D91216) (Box 166, Folder 10)
  - London Business School (G96109) (Box 166, Folder 11)
  - London Business School (G97226) (Box 166, Folder 12-14)
  - M - General, 1989-1996 (Box 166, Folder 15-21)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 1984-1996 (Box 166, Folder 22-26)
  - MacNeil-Lehrer NewsHuor, 1991-1992 (Box 166, Folder 27)
  - MacMurray College, 1970 (Box 166, Folder 28)
  - Macy Foundation, 1975-1983 (Box 166, Folder 29)
  - Burton Malkeil, 1990 (Box 166, Folder 30)
  - Manhattan Cable, 1971-1972 (Box 166, Folder 31)
  - Mac World, 1993-1994 (Box 166, Folder 32-33)
  - Manhattan Institute - Hammett (D94219), 1993-1998 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Manhattan Institute - Huber (D93114), 1992-1996 (Box 167, Folder 2-3)
  - Manhattan Institute, 1989-1996 (Box 167, Folder 4-11)
  - Markle Foundation - Markle Commission Follow-Up (G92334), 1992-1997 (Box 167, Folder 12-14)
  - Markle Foundation - Fleishman-Hillard (DJ99335), 1999 (Box 167, Folder 15)
  - Markle Foundation - Communications Technology Study (G92339), 1992-1995 (Box 167, Folder 16-17)
  - Markle Foundation - Political Advertising Study (G92335), 1992-1994 (Box 167, Folder 18-19)
  - Markle Foundation - CNN (G92222) - Program Related Expenses, 1992-1993 (Box 168, Folder 19-22)
  - Markle Foundation - SeniorNet (G90216, G90324) (Box 168, Folder 23-24)
  - Markle Foundation - SeniorNet (D92103) (Box 168, Folder 25)
  - Markle Foundation - Special Interest Cable Channel (D92101), 1991-1992 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Markle Foundation - Public Edu Project (G91329), 1991-1992 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Markle Foundation - Electronic Book Research Project (D91325), 1991-1993 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Markle Foundation - Brown and Powers (G91112), 1990-1992 (Box 169, Folder 4-6)
  - Markle Foundation - Electronic Text Conference (D91104), 1990-1993 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - Markle Foundation - SeniorNet (G90324), 1990-1992 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Markle Foundation - Brown and Powers (G90325), 1990-1991 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Markle Foundation (G90323) - Fundraising Activities and Outreach, 1991 (Box 169, Folder 10-12)
  - Markle Scholars in Academic Medicine - 50th Anniversary Meeting - Preparations and Arrangements, 1998 (Box 169, Folder 13-22)
  - Markle Foundation - Readings in Information and Communications Policy - Monroe Price, 1997-1999 (Box 169, Folder 23-25)
  - Markle Foundation - "High Fever" - An Educational Multimedia Game (J98005), 1997-1998 (Box 170, Folder 1-5)
  - Markle Foundation - Expanding Outreach (DJ99110), 1998-1999 (Box 170, Folder 6-7)
  - Markle Foundation - Children and Communications (DJ99104), 1998-1999 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Markle Foundation - Accuracy in Journalism (J98337), 1998-1999 (Box 170, Folder 9-11)
  - Markle Foundation - Universal Access (DJ112) (Box 170, Folder 13-15)
  - Markle Foundation - Democracy Net (D98224) (Box 170, Folder 16)
  - Markle Foundation - Governor's Working Group on Technology (D98225), 1998-1999 (Box 170, Folder 17)
  - Markle Foundation - "High Fever" (D98020), 1997-1998 (Box 170, Folder 18)
  - Markle Foundation - FCC Meeting (D98218), 1997 (Box 170, Folder 19)
  - Markle Foundation - Arlen Communications (J98111), 1997-1998 (Box 170, Folder 20)
  - Markle Scholars in Academic Medicine - 50th Reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 171, Folder 1-2)
  - Markle Foundation - Pubic Radio International (D98101), 1997-1998 (Box 171, Folder 3-4)
  - Markle Foundation - Media in Transition (J97334), 1997-1999 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Markle Foundation - High Fever (D97331), 1997-1998 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Markle Foundation - Bellcore (D97223) (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Markle Foundation - Changing Channels (D97217), 1997 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Markle Foundation - Fast Forward (J97021), 1997-1998 (Box 172, Folder 6-7)
  - Markle Foundation - Book Projects - Transition in Administration Projects (D97012) (Box 172, Folder 8-9)
  - Markle Foundation - Interactive Educational Games (J97111), 1996-1997 (Box 172, Folder 10-11)
  - Markle Foundation - Research on Moral Basis of Broadcasting (D97101), 1996-1998 (Box 172, Folder 12-13)
  - Markle Fellow - Monroe Price (J96338) (Box 172, Folder 14-15)
  - Markle Foundation - Interactive Storytelling Project (J96335), 1996-1998 (Box 172, Folder 16)
  - Markle Foundation - Interactive Storytelling Project (J96335), 1996-1998; Includes CDs. (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Markle Foundation - Wunderman Cato Johnson (J96331), 1996-1998 (Box 173, Folder 2-3)
  - Markle Foundation - Universal Email (J96330), 1996-1998 (Box 173, Folder 4-5)
  - Markle Foundation - Bellcore (D96329) (Box 173, Folder 6-8)
  - Markle Foundation - Interactive Storytelling Project (J96325), 1996-1997 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Markle Foundation - Interactive Storytelling Project (J96324), 1996-1997 (Box 173, Folder 10)
  - Markle Foundation - Voyager Corporation (D96322), 1996 (Box 173, Folder 11)
  - Markle Foundation - Commission Follow-Up (J96217), 1996-1999 (Box 173, Folder 12-14)
  - 2017:FA785:010 - Markle Foundation - Commission Follow-Up (J96217) - Audio, 1998 June 12; Audio. (Box 2017:FA785:010)
  - Markle Foundation - Programmer Free Software (D97215), 1996-1997 (Box 173, Folder 16)
  - Markle Foundation - Interactive Storytelling Project (D96213), 1995-1996 (Box 173, Folder 17)
  - Markle Foundation - Reinventing America II (REUS II) (J96026), 1996-1997 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Markle Foundation - Reinventing America - Presidential Election '96 - Promotion (J96110), 1995-1997 (Box 174, Folder 2-3)
  - Markle Foundation - Election '96 - Development and Promotion (J95329), 1995 (Box 174, Folder 4-5)
  - Markle Foundation - Commission Follow-Up (J95327), 1995-1997 (Box 174, Folder 6-8)
  - Markle Foundation - Interactive Storytelling Project (J96005) (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - Markle Foundation - Adoption of New Communications Technology (G92225), 1992-1998 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Markle Fellow - Henry Geller (G89214), 1991-1994 (Box 174, Folder 11)